https://www.fend.org/content/terms-and-conditions-and-privacy-policy

Skip to main content
User menu
Log in
Foundation of European Nurses in Diabetes
The pan European non-profit organisation for nurses working in the specialty of diabetes
Terms and Conditions
Cancellation PolicyRefund of conference registration fees:  • Before 11 July 2018: 100%  • 11 July - 11 August 2018: 50%  • After 11 August 2018: None
Liability and InsuranceThe Conference Secretariat and Organizers cannot accept liability for personal accidents or loss of or damage to private property of participants and accompanying persons, either during or indirectly arising from the FEND Annual Conference. Participants are advised to take out their own personal health and travel insurance for their trip.
Privacy Policy
FEND is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Policy explains when and why we collect personal information about you, how we use it and how we keep it secure.
Any questions regarding this Policy and our privacy practices should be sent by email to info@fend.org or by writing to FEND, 24 Holmesdale Avenue, London SW14 7BQ.
Who are we?
We’re FEND, an association dedicated to nurses in Europe who specialise in diabetes. FEND is a registered charity (no. 1134995) and company limited by guarantee (no. 7114723). The registered address is 37 Earls Drive, Newcastle On Tyne, NE15 7AL, UK.
How do we collect information from you?
We obtain information about you when you complete the membership application or conference registration forms and when you make online payment.
What type of information is collected from you?
The personal information we collect might include your name, address, email address, IP address. If you make a payment online, your card information is not held by FEND, it is collected by our third party payment processors, who specialise in the secure online capture and processing of credit/debit card transactions.
How is your information used?
We may use your information to:
process a payment that you have made
process orders that you have submitted
to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into by you and us
dealing with entries into a survey or competition
seek your views or comments on the services we provide
notify you of changes to our services
send you communications which you have requested
We review our retention periods for personal information on a regular basis. We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you are a member or as long as is necessary for the relevant activity, whichever is the longer.
Who has access to your information?
We will not sell or rent your information to other parties.
Third Party Service Providers working on our behalf:
We may pass your information to our third party service providers for the purposes of completing tasks and providing services to you on our behalf (for example to process payments). However, when we use third party service providers, we disclose only the personal information that is necessary to deliver the service and we have a contract in place that requires them to keep your information secure.
When you are using our secure online payment pages, your donation is processed by a third party payment processor, SagePay EU, who specialises in the secure online capture and processing of credit/debit card transactions. If you have any questions regarding secure transactions, please contact us.
Your choices
You have a choice about whether or not you wish to receive information from us. If you do not want to receive direct communications from us about our events and services, then you can select your choices by ticking the relevant boxes situated on your profile page.
How you can access and update your information
The accuracy of your information is important to us. If you change email address, or any of the other information we hold about you you should update your information on your profile page.
Security precautions in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of your information
When you give us personal information, we take steps to ensure that it’s treated securely. Data is encrypted and protected during transmission with 128 Bit encryption on SSL. All FEND website pages are secured in this way, indicated by a lock icon or similar depending on which browser you use.
You are responsible for keeping your login password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.
Review of this Policy
We keep this Policy under regular review. This Policy was last updated 25 April 2018.
© FEND 2014-2017 | Contact | Privacy Policy | Tel: +44 (0)20 8876 6122 Registered Charity no. 1134995.  Company limited by guarantee. Registered in England no. 7114723, Registered office: 37 Earls Drive, Newcastle On Tyne, NE15 7AL, UK
